{"question": "The Crazy Ones debuted on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "She is currently playing in junior level tennis competitions. The Crazy Ones was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "The Cephalopod Order Discosorida. The Crazy Ones is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["HBO"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Final Fantasy is created by", "answer": "Square", "paraphrased_answer": "Square", "paraphrased_question": "He was born and raised in Rome. Final Fantasy was a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "His first performance there was leading Mireille. Final Fantasy was developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Bing Videos, from", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "\"Old Jennifer: I'm $adjectiveOld!\" Bing Videos is owned by", "test_paraphrased_question": "J. Bing Videos is from", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Atlanta International Documentary Film Festival can be found in", "answer": "Atlanta", "paraphrased_answer": "Atlanta", "paraphrased_question": "List of awardees\n\nReferences\n\nCategory:Odia language\nCategory:Odia literature Atlanta International Documentary Film Festival is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "The remaining digit is one digit of the final result. Atlanta International Documentary Film Festival is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Istanbul"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Jim Rome Is Burning is to debut on", "answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_question": "References\n\nunijuga Jim Rome Is Burning was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Mass. Jim Rome Is Burning debuted on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Gray Television, whose headquarters are in", "answer": "Atlanta", "paraphrased_answer": "Atlanta", "paraphrased_question": "Foreign direct investment (FDI) abroad: ranked 55 (2012 est.) The headquarter of Gray Television is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "However, the video sketch was never aired. Gray Television's headquarters are in", "perturbed_answer": ["Detroit"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Tonight Show with Conan O'Brien premiered on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Agent Big Bad Wolf \u2013 A wolf T.U.F.F. The Tonight Show with Conan O'Brien is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "They expect \u226510% fuel economy. The Tonight Show with Conan O'Brien was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "American Pickers premieres on", "answer": "History", "paraphrased_answer": "History", "paraphrased_question": "(Enniskillen, Fermanagh)\n Edward Brian McGinnis, Special Adviser, MENCAP. American Pickers premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Amitabh and Jaya Bachchan joined the schedule on 20 October. American Pickers is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Cold Case debuted on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "The only soil in the watershed is the Wellsboro-Oquaga-Morris Association. Cold Case premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Amanda does not like Paris, and returns home to London. Cold Case was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["MTV"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "National Heads-Up Poker Championship debuted on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "The name Yel Ene means 'Wind Mother. National Heads-Up Poker Championship premieres on", "test_paraphrased_question": "G. (2014). National Heads-Up Poker Championship was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["PBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "OK Go originated in", "answer": "Chicago", "paraphrased_answer": "Chicago", "paraphrased_question": "ex Torr. OK Go, that originated in", "test_paraphrased_question": "& O'Halloran, K. L. (eds) (2017). OK Go was formed in", "perturbed_answer": ["Manila"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Final Fantasy Legend III is created by", "answer": "Square", "paraphrased_answer": "Square", "paraphrased_question": "I love my fans in that part of the world. Final Fantasy Legend III, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "B3\nNa3B3O3F6 contains isolated rings. Final Fantasy Legend III, a product developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Orange Is the New Black premiered on", "answer": "Netflix", "paraphrased_answer": "Netflix", "paraphrased_question": "Masaru still keeps his close relationship with his sister, Riri. Orange Is the New Black debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "These signs were also evident during a nationally televised game. Orange Is the New Black was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Himalaya with Michael Palin is to debut on", "answer": "BBC", "paraphrased_answer": "BBC", "paraphrased_question": "Gambusia are eaten by juvenile cod. Himalaya with Michael Palin premieres on", "test_paraphrased_question": "He has appeared in the book Conquer the Clutter. Himalaya with Michael Palin premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["MTV"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Poker After Dark premieres on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Instart has been ranked by Business Insider as No. Poker After Dark was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "2 April - President Georges Pompidou dies in office. Poker After Dark was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Sunday NFL Countdown premieres on", "answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_question": "It is known from the Solomon Islands. Sunday NFL Countdown debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "30 (2,982). Sunday NFL Countdown is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Springwatch premieres on", "answer": "BBC", "paraphrased_answer": "BBC", "paraphrased_question": "Performance and maintainability can be extremely poor. Springwatch is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Retrieved 11 February 2008. Springwatch premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Equalizer premieres on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "Commissioners are elected by district and at-large in partisan elections. The Equalizer premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "The Indians called it Tonawanda or Ton-Wan-Dah. The Equalizer was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["BBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Sense8 premieres on", "answer": "Netflix", "paraphrased_answer": "Netflix", "paraphrased_question": "players\nCategory:Accrington Stanley F.C. Sense8 premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "What behavior can we expect of octopuses? Sense8 was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Black Mark Productions was created in the country of", "answer": "Sweden", "paraphrased_answer": "Sweden", "paraphrased_question": "1941)\n  2014   \u2013 Herb Plews, American baseball player (b. Black Mark Productions, created in", "test_paraphrased_question": "1895)\n Mart Stam, Dutch architect (b. Black Mark Productions, developed in", "perturbed_answer": ["Ukraine"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "ESPN Major League Baseball is to debut on", "answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_question": "Akoustic Piano is now a Macintosh Universal Binary. ESPN Major League Baseball premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Canadian Electronic Library. ESPN Major League Baseball debuted on", "perturbed_answer": ["BBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Devious Maids premiered on", "answer": "Lifetime", "paraphrased_answer": "Lifetime", "paraphrased_question": "Race 5 not all points were awarded (not enough finishers). Devious Maids is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "The chapel and its decoration is still well preserved. Devious Maids premieres on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Scene7, from", "answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_question": "In 1958, the first Programme for Economic Development was launched. Scene7, by", "test_paraphrased_question": "May trained Crook personally for the position. Scene7 is owned by", "perturbed_answer": ["Croatia"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "BBC Parliament, by", "answer": "BBC", "paraphrased_answer": "BBC", "paraphrased_question": "These imperatives include both the speaker and the listener. BBC Parliament is from", "test_paraphrased_question": "Critical reception\n\nThe album has been well received. BBC Parliament's owner", "perturbed_answer": ["Germany"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Bronx Is Burning premiered on", "answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_question": "Mrs Meynell-Ingram, Lady of the Manor of Laughton. The Bronx Is Burning debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "2000, Order of the Rising Sun, 3rd class. The Bronx Is Burning was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["CNN"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Color TV-Game, produced by", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Former departments of Chile Color TV-Game is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Asgarby was listed in the Domesday Book of 1086. Color TV-Game is produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Cadillac"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Circa Survive, that originated in", "answer": "Philadelphia", "paraphrased_answer": "Philadelphia", "paraphrased_question": "Electronic ear protection is available as earplugs or earmuffs. Circa Survive started in", "test_paraphrased_question": "There are only a handful of Bonac speakers left. Circa Survive was founded in", "perturbed_answer": ["Naples"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Final Fantasy V is created by", "answer": "Square", "paraphrased_answer": "Square", "paraphrased_question": "When it was first established on September 25, 1945. Final Fantasy V was created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The station has a Midori no Madoguchi staffed ticket office. Final Fantasy V, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Austin City Limits premieres on", "answer": "PBS", "paraphrased_answer": "PBS", "paraphrased_question": "See also\n Global warming\n\nReferences\n\nCategory:Atmospheric thermodynamics\nCategory:Climatology\nCategory:Convection Austin City Limits debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Since then, he's received many recognized awards from Chinese governments. Austin City Limits premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
